{
    "id": "de5d536da1a0411799626e6fc9f024b5",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Hold And Keep",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9c449abd35244b019bb3ef417221c403",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He was called Christy .................................................... his grandfather who had died in the civil war.",
                    "description": "Call after = be named after somebody",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "after",
                        "around"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is not much ............................................ air-conditioners during the winter season.",
                    "description": "Call for = demand\r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "call in",
                        "call on",
                        "call for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This remarkable achievement ........................................... a celebration.",
                    "description": "Call for = demand, require",
                    "answers": [
                        "calls in",
                        "calls off",
                        "calls for",
                        "calls out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This spike in property prices forced us to ........................................... buying a new apartment.",
                    "description": "Hold off = delay",
                    "answers": [
                        "hold off",
                        "hold on",
                        "hold to",
                        "hold with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you ............................................. people who live together before they get married?",
                    "description": "Hold with = accept or agree\r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "hold on",
                        "hold out on",
                        "hold with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We were ................................................. by the traffic jam.",
                    "description": "Hold up = delay while traveling",
                    "answers": [
                        "held out",
                        "held up",
                        "held on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She likes to .................................................... old clothes for some strange reason",
                    "description": "To hold onto something is to keep it longer than necessary",
                    "answers": [
                        "hold together",
                        "hold off",
                        "hold onto"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ your hands. I am going to inspect your finger nails",
                    "description": "To hold out is to extend in front of you",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hold on",
                        "Hold out",
                        "Hold off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The strikers .................................................. until the management agreed to give them what they wanted.",
                    "description": "To hold out is to resist / protest. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "held up",
                        "held off",
                        "held out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................. the rope. I am going to pull you up.",
                    "description": "To hold onto something is to grip it tightly",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hold onto",
                        "Hold over",
                        "Hold on",
                        "Hold at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very ill. She can't .............................................. even water.",
                    "description": "To keep food down is to keep it in the stomach without vomiting.",
                    "answers": [
                        "keep at",
                        "keep in",
                        "keep down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The police ............................................ the protesters .............................................. by blocking the road.",
                    "description": "To keep somebody back is to keep them at a safe distance.",
                    "answers": [
                        "kept, back",
                        "kept, away",
                        "kept, at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}